

NGUYEN VAN A

MARKETING MANAGER

Male

May 19, 1992

Hanoi, Vietnam

fb.com/quynhtom design

Take advantages of sales skills & experience and ectetur adipiscing elit, sed do eiusmod tempor incididunt ut labore et dolore magna aliqua of market to become a professional Sales Staff and bring a lot value to Customers. From that, I will contribute to development of CVPRO Company.

EDUCATION



FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. our, or random administration

mm Sep 2007 - Present

FOREIGN TRADE UNIVERSITY

major. corporate administration

m Sep 2007 - Present

EXPERIENCE



Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult iece of classical and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

Sep 2007 - Present

CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

Main responsibilities:

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer customers' queries via phone and email.
- Assist to selecting type for a galley TYPESETTER SELE goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

Recognition and Gains:

- Advertising products of the Company to customers effectively: contribute to a 20% increase in the number of customers within one month of working

ACTIVITIES Sep 2003 - 2007



CVPRO JSC

Sale Executive

- Write and upload product advertising post via Facebook, Forum...
- Introduce, consult products and answer because it is pleasure, but because those who do not know how to pursue pleasure rationally 'queries via phone and email.
- Assist to control goods in and out
- Attend Sales Skill Course in the Company

CERTIFICATIONS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2004

HONORS & AWARDS



TOEIC Certificate With Score 800 Issued By CVPRO 2013 - 2014

ADDITIONAL INFORMATION



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt scholarships and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US imes you don't want to pay \$400/hr. Not to mention, Cupcake Ipsum, Bob Ross Ipsum ("hap

REFERENCES



NGUYEN VAN BINH

director of cvpro jsc

SKILLS





INTERESTS



- Organize monthly events, network with US alumni
- Share how to hunt thứ 16 và được tái bản sau đó cho những người quan tâm đến nó. Đoạn 1.10.32 và 1.10.33 trong cuốn and US student's life experiences to all students who have received offers from US universities